Jacob G. Lepler

www.jacoblepler.com

CONTACT

(301) 312-7151



Lepler.Jacob@gmail.com



7012 Richard Drive Bethesda, MD, 20817



EDUCATION

2019 - Present

B.S. Software Development & Security University of Maryland - Global Campus

2019

Java Web Development Boot Camp Montgomery College - Gaithersburg, MD

SKILLS & Competencies

HTML & CSS Javascript ReactJS, Java, Spring MVC, JSX, React Redux, Bootstrap Materialize

- Excellent Organizational Skills
- Strong oral and written competency
- Ability to work in a team or independently
- Excellent written / oral communication skills

PROFILE

Highly motivated Web Developer with 10+ years of customer service and hospitality experience. Collaboratively and individually persistent and results driven developer with hundreds of hours of personal study, and Bootcamp style training in various web development (full-stack) competencies.

EXPERIENCE

2019 - Present

Freelance Web Developer

- Design/Coded 2 Client sites
- Increase in sales through user-friendly design and layout
- Implemented color theory, to convey specific need

2015 - Present

Mangiare, Inc. - Positano Ristorante Italiano - Server

- Coordinate banquets for up to 200 guests
- Train new servers on policy and procedures
- Work with kitchen, management, and other servers to successfully operate and manage parties
- Developed close rapport with both new and frequent customers
- Operating both regular dining and parties (including Bar/Bat Mitzvahs, Holiday Parties, Birthdays, Reunions, and more)

2016-2018

Capitol Visa - Customer Support/Quality Assurance Specialist

- Coordinate with senior project manager to deliver timely travel document processing
- Deliver process completion within client deadlines
- Respond to new inquiries by email and phone
- Receive and file new customer requests into company database
- Stay up to date on over 100 embassy processing procedures

2013-2016

Starbucks Corporation - Store Supervisor

- Manage employee's schedule / Clerical
- Delegating task and assigning duties
- Create seamless customer friendly environment
- Mitigating all areas of customer relations
- Submit orders for food and beverage products
- Certified in Maryland Food Safety management